http://www.pornstarnetwork.com/privacy.html

Live
Anal SexAsianBabesBBWBig TitsBlondeBondageBrunetteCollege GirlsCouplesCurvyEbonyGrannyGroup SexHairy PussyHousewivesHuge TitsLatinaLeatherLesbianMatureMedium TitsPetite BodyPornstarRedheadShaved PussySmall TitsTeen 18+ToysTrimmed PussyWhite Girls
Studios
DVDs
Sites
Reviews
Discount
Advanced
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices about the way your information is collected and used. To ensure this notice easy to find, we ensure it is available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this site and other sites part or our network. This Privacy Policy applies to the information we collect on the site, both mobile and desktop versions. It also applies for any correspondance between this site, the administrators, and you. For example, this may include communication by email or text. As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time and the effective date listed with it. Should you have any questions about this policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer by submitting a ticket through our support page.
Adults Only Service
This is an adult site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. This site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents on this site without exception. If you are under the age of 18 and/or under the age of majority in the jurisdiction you reside and from which you access the website, then your account will be terminated without notice or delay.
Information We Collect From You
Personal data, or personal information, pertains to any information about an individual from which that person can be identified by.
It does not include data that has been rendered anonymous.
Any customer that joins/signs up as a subscriber of the site will be required to provide some personal information.
Information may include:
Technical Data such as:
the visitor's IP address
browser type and version
time zone setting and location
operating system and platform
information on device used to access the website
User-submitted Data which includes data collected following a specific action the user has taken, such as filling out information for a survey
Usage Data which includes aggregated information about how you use the website
Marketing and Communications Data includes your communication preferences and also your preference in receiving marketing from us and our third parties.
Cookies: When you visit the website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. The website uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookies, some of the site's features may not function properly.
Log File Information: When you visit the site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.
Identity Data such as:
Username
Password
Email address
Address including street number, street, city, State/Province, Country, Zip/Postal Code
Use of Personal Information
We may use "cookies" and Demographic Information to better your experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Sites according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Demographic Information. Examples of cookies that are used on this site:
Cookies that are strictly necessary: These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Website. These include, for example, cookies that enable a user to log in to our Website and to check if a user is allowed access to a particular service or content.
Analytical cookies: These cookies allow us to recognize and count the number of users and to see how users use and explore our Website. These cookies help us to improve our Website, for example by ensuring that all users are able to find what they are looking for easily.
Functionality cookies: These cookies are not essential, but help us to personalize and enhance your online experience on our Website. This type of cookies allows us to recognize you when you return to our Website and to remember, for example, your choice of language.
Targeting cookies: These cookies record the visit of a user on our Website, the pages a user has visited and the links a user has followed in order to enable us to ensure our Website is more relevant to the users' interests.
We do not require that you accept cookies and you may withdraw your consent to our use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browserâ€™s privacy settings. However, if you decline to accept cookies, some functionality on our Website may be disabled and you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires automatically when you close your browser. A persistent cookie will remain until it expires or you delete your cookies. Expiration dates are set in the cookies themselves; some may expire after a few minutes while others may expire after multiple years.
Aggregate, non-individual membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in. The site may also automatically collect traffic and click-through data as well as information regarding the online behaviour of subscribers by the use of "cookies" or other programming means - any information about subscribers collected by the site through the use of cookies or other programming means will generally not be attributable to the specific user in any way. We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Sites. If the site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a subscriber of the site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the subscriber voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the site and included in its customer database. If a subscriber sends any personal communication or correspondence by any means, to the site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the site may collect the information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database. Financial Data will only be shared with third party processors as necessary to initiate and complete any orders placed by your account.
Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. Unless expressly stated otherwise, our website does not provide any Personal Information to these third parties, however they may collect information, including Personal Information, such as internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content.
We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
How we Use Your Personal Information
The personally identifiable information you submit to the Website is used to provide the user with special, personalized site features.
We may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages.
We may use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).
Opt-in communication - Subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his/her email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him/her offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with the option to express the subscriber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes", the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information, including its email address and data may be used for that matter.
Opt-out communication - Subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his/her email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may not be used to send him/her offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications.
We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the Website user-experience.
Examples of this may include collecting your Usage Data to determine what percentage of all users visited a certain page.
Disclosure of Information
Your name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary fulfill technical requirement or to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system.
We do not share your personally identifiable information, such as email address, with other third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent, or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.
We may disclose your personal information to authorized service providers that perform services on our behalf.
These services may include but are not limited to 3rd party email management software, fulfillment of orders, providing customer service, performing business or sales analysis, and aggregated data analysis software.
We may also disclose your information in the case where there is a lawful successor.
In the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or any other type of sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, the information in our possession may be transferred to the successor.
We may disclose aggregated information about our users which does not identify any individual, without any restriction.
Transfers of Your Personal Information to Other Countries
Whenever in the course of sharing information we transfer Personal Information to countries outside of the EU and other regions with comprehensive data protection laws, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this privacy policy and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection.
For example, data may need to be transferred outside of the EU region in order to facilitate transactional data with acquiring banks, payment gateways, payment processors, and/or card associations.
By using the Website you consent to the transfer of information that we collect about you, including personal information, to any country in which we or our service providers are located.
Financial Information
All financial data will only be shared with the site's third party processors in order to initiate and complete any orders placed on your account. All credit card transactions and such are processed with industry standard encryption through third party processors. Said processors only use your information for that purpose. All financial data and information shall be considered private information and will not be shared by the site with third parties except with your authorization or when necessary to carry out all and any transactions requested by the user with the understanding that such transactions may be subject to rules, terms, conditions and policies of a third party. All such information provided to a third party and all transactions are not governed by this Privacy Policy. All such information provided to a third party is subject to their terms and conditions.
Security of Information
We has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to subscribers that is collected by the site.
While we uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. All subscribers should consider any information provided to or collected by the site as non-confidential, and consequently the site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.
Advertisements
We utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or "action tags" to measure advertising effectiveness on an "anonymous basis". Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the Sites. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we cannot, and do not, provide any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers' websites. If you choose to complete any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including Financial Data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, provide any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or emails, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of the Sites on such advertisers' website(s).
YOUR RIGHTS
All registered users may review, update, correct or delete the personal information in their account by contacting us or by editing your profile via the site. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.
In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation law in the EU effective May 25, 2018, users of this site may request a copy of their personal data as well as request that their personal data be deleted.
Official identification shall be required to confirm your identity.
In order to formulate such a request, contact our Data Protection Officer by submitting a request through our support page.
Disclaimer
By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may use any personal information that has been provided by the subscriber or that has been collected by the site about the subscriber for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administrative, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading of personal data, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the site or third parties authorized to use the information by the site.
By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about subscribers that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.
All personal information about a subscriber may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the site.
The site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a subscriber may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the site. The site shall not be responsible for the privacy policy or the content of other such websites. This site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or privacy policies of any of those third-party websites.
Whenever applicable, each subscriber should seek to read the privacy policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the site.
All information collected may be shared when necessary to comply with applicable law and /or to cooperate with law enforcement agencies and the courts/tribunals.
Changes and Modification to the Privacy Policy
We may change this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating otherwise.
Changes in the Ownership of the Sites
We are a growing online service. As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including but not limited to merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us (including Financial Data and Account Information) with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such transaction(s).
Terms and Conditions of the Sites
Each subscriber should carefully read each of the terms and conditions of the site. By accepting membership to this site, you are unconditionally accepting all of these terms and conditions. Some of these terms and conditions may also affect the right of this site to use information that it has gathered from subscribers.
Privacy
FAQ
Support
Terms
DMCA
Affiliates
Site Map
18 U.S.C. 2257 Record-Keeping Requirement Compliance Statement
Pornstar Network © 2020
